nativex.com 2012-12-27

# Privacy Policy

Glad to see that you are a cautious/smart online shopper and look at terms. We want you to have a safe and private shopping experience with NATIVE(X). If you want the lawyer details, read below. 

Privacy Policy- Privacy Matters!  
Please take some time to review NATIVE(X)’s policy for handling your information. When visiting the NATIVE(X) website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. NATIVE(X)’s Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please revisit this page and review the Policy regularly. If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us via e-mail at mac@nativex.com. We look forward to your questions, comments, and suggestions. 

As detailed below, NATIVE(X) may share the information it collects with third parties. We may use the collected information to improve the content of our website, to improve future marketing efforts, to notify you about current NATIVE(X) products, special offers, services and events, and for other purposes. The information we collect may be combined with other personally identifiable information available from our records and other sources, such as purchase history. 

We ask only for the information we need to process your requests:

### Postal Address

If you purchase from us you will need to enter your postal address via our paypal shopping cart. We will not distribute or sell your address to any third party.

### Credit Card Information

To purchase from the NATIVE(X) website, you will need to either enter your paypal information or your credit card number through our secure paypal checkout terminal. This information is kept encrypted to ensure secure purchases. This is secure information and cannot be accessed by anyone other than the account holder. Please see PayPal’s policies for full details. [Paypal Legal Documents](https://cms.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Legal_Hub_popup)

### E-Mail Address

If you would like to receive e-mail on what's happening at NATIVE(X), fill out our e-mail registration located on the footer of our webpage, and we will add you to our mailing list. If you subscribe to NATIVE(X)’s e-mail list, we will send you periodic updates and news about our website. Hopefully you will find these updates fun and intriguing. If you have any ideas or recommendations for our newsletter email us at mac@nativex.com. Please be assured that the e-mail address you provide to NATIVE(X) is for internal use only.

### Questions and Comments:

We want to hear from you -- your comments, suggestions, questions. Every message is read and a response sent as quickly as possible if requested. The information you send us is used to respond to your questions and comments only. You may send your comments, suggestions or questions to mac@nativex.com

### Cookies:

NATIVE(X) may also use "cookies" or other means to passively collect information about your use of our website. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your computer that lets your web browser talk with NATIVE(X)’s web server. It saves you from retyping your user name and password every time you use our secure checkout.

### Children:

The NATIVE(X) website is intended only for those aged 13 and older. If you are under 13, you may not register or submit personally identifiable information on, to or through the site. NATIVE(X) does not collect personally identifiable information from any person NATIVE(X) knows to be under 13.

### Google Site Stats:

You may have clicked on an ad for this website that was delivered by Google.

### Relevant Ads, Quality Advertisers

Google measures the performance of the advertising it delivers. By providing a tool to more accurately measure the performance of the ads we deliver, Google (and advertisers) will be able to improve the quality and relevance of the ads that you see.

### Your Privacy

To measure performance, Google uses small strings of text (known as cookies) that are placed on your computer when you click on ads. Cookies typically remain active on your computer for about 30 days. If you visit certain pages of the advertiser's website during that period, Google and the advertiser will be able to tell that you saw the ad delivered by Google.  
If you'd like to know more about how Google handles information gathered from the use of cookies, please read our privacy policy. If you want to disable the use of cookies, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some websites may not function properly if you refuse to accept cookies.
